All right. You're done. Let's look at the solution. All
好的，完成啦，让我们看看结果。
right. We'll move to WeatherProvider. We start by creating a
我们回来WeatherProvider。 让我们来创建
third selection query up at the top of our provider,
第三个选项查询，
much like the second query except that we search for
跟第二个查询差不多一样，是一个需要特定日期的
the exact date. Rather than a greater than or equal
查询。 我们这次不要放大于或等于输入
date. We then add a function that uses the weather
日期。 我们加入一个用天气合约的
contract. Functions to get the date and postal code from
函数。 这些函数会通过URI来获取时期和
the URI. We use the new query we just wrote.
邮编。我们来调用我们刚刚写新查询。
And the same SQLI query builder we used before, since it only defines the join.
同时我们会使用我们之前使用的SQLI查询创建者，这个创建者是用来定义join的。
And then we just call this function in the
然后我们就调用这个函数。这个函数
weather with location and date switch statement in our
通过天气与地点，同时包括日期进行交换
query. That's it. Those are all the queries we
查询。 就这么简单。 这就是我们所有的用来
plan to use for Sunshine, but we still need to
查询Sunshine的计划了。 但是别高兴太早，我们还需要
test. Let's go back to test provider. As you
检查一下。 调回test provider类。
can see, our test has a very, very good model
你看，我们已经有了一个非常，非常赞的模型。
already. Let's fix up some of these old tests
现在我们需要来修改一些久的测试
and close the weather cursor. Now, we can simply copy
同时我们关闭天气光标。 然后我们就轻松复制这些
this test over. It turns out that the exact
测试。 看这些数据跟我们新的URI里
same data is required for our new URI. All
要求的数据意义。 最后我们
we have to do is to build weather location
只需要做的是创建一个天气地点和时间的
with date, instead of saying weather location with start
参数，而不是天气地点和开始时间的参数
date, and we should get the same result. Let's
，结果应该是一样的。 下一步的测试就是见证
see if that's really true by running our tests.
奇迹的时刻。
[SOUND] And our test passed. So, we've now implemented
我们的测试成功通过。 所以哪，我们所有的执行的
all of the queries, but we're not done with our
查询都过通过了，不过我们还有一点关于 content provider
content provider yet. After all, we're not writing
需要处理。毕竟，我们还没通过我么的
any data into the database through our content provider
content provider 把任何的数据放入我们的数据库。